<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fixeds on Dr. Hannah Roberts</title><link>https://heroberts.github.io/fixed/</link><description>Recent content in Fixeds on Dr. Hannah Roberts</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://heroberts.github.io/fixed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://heroberts.github.io/fixed/home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://heroberts.github.io/fixed/home/</guid><description>Hi! This site now serves as an archive of sorts of my academic work. Here you can find links to my papers as well as details you&amp;rsquo;d find on my academic CV. Feel free to get in touch if any of my previous work is of interest.
Links Email Twitter LinkedIn Github Google Scholar ORCID</description></item><item><title>Education</title><link>https://heroberts.github.io/education/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://heroberts.github.io/education/</guid><description>PhD in Psychology, Jan 2018. Development and Evaluation of Environmental Interventions on Green Space Utilisation to Promote Health and Well-being. University of Leeds. [pdf]
MSc in Geographical Information Systems, 2014. University of Leeds.
BA in Geography, 2013. University of Sheffield.</description></item><item><title>Publications</title><link>https://heroberts.github.io/publications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://heroberts.github.io/publications/</guid><description>Roberts, H., &amp;amp; Helbich, M. (2021). Multiple environmental exposures along daily mobility paths and depressive symptoms: a smartphone-based tracking study. Environment International, 156, 106635. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.envint.2021.106635 [osf project]
Roberts, H., van Lissa, C., &amp;amp; Helbich, M. (2020). Perceived neighbourhood characteristics and depressive symptoms: Potential mediators and the moderating role of employment status. Social Science &amp;amp; Medicine, 268, 113533. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.socscimed.2020.113533 [osf project]
Lan, Y., Roberts, H., Kwan, M.</description></item><item><title>Presentations</title><link>https://heroberts.github.io/presentations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://heroberts.github.io/presentations/</guid><description>Invited Talks Roberts, H. (2021). Residential- and mobility-based environmental exposures and depressive symptoms. Invited talk for ODISSEI. Virtual.
Roberts, H., van Lissa, C., Hagedoorn, P., Kellar, I., Helbich, M. (2019). The effect of short-term exposure to the natural environment on depressive mood: A systematic review and meta-analysis. Oral presentation given at Human Geography and Spatial Planning Research Days. Zwolle, the Netherlands.
Roberts, H. (2016) Developing an environmental intervention to increase green space utilisation in order to promote health.</description></item><item><title>Teaching</title><link>https://heroberts.github.io/teaching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://heroberts.github.io/teaching/</guid><description>Bachelor-level courses As teaching assistant unless otherwise specified Geographies of Health, Department of Human Geography and Spatial Planning, Utrecht University (2018/19; 2019/20; 2020/21) (Co-meeting leader, guest lecturer) Urban Geography, University College Utrecht (2019/20; 2020/21) (Guest lecturer) Psychology Research Skills 1, School of Psychology, University of Leeds (2015/16) (Seminar Leader) GIS and Spatial Analysis, School of Geography, University of Leeds, (2014/15; 2015/16; 2016/17) Programming for Geographical Information Analysis: Core Skills, School of Geography, University of Leeds (2014/15) Programming for Geographical Information Analysis: Advanced Skills, School of Geography, University of Leeds (2014/15) Master-level courses Applied GIS and Retail Modelling, School of Geography, University of Leeds (2016/17) Systematic Research Review, School of Psychology, University of Leeds (2015/16; 2016/17) Postgraduate courses Computer Programming for Social Scientists (1-week course) (2014; 2015) ArcGIS for Transport Studies (2-day course) (2015) Supervision Bachelor thesis (Department of Human Geography and Spatial Planning; Utrecht University) (2020/21 x 2) Master thesis (Department of Human Geography and Spatial Planning; Utrecht University) (2018/19 x 3; 2019/20 x 3; 2020/21 x 2) Bachelor thesis (Utrecht College Utrecht) (2019/20 x 1)</description></item><item><title>Other Activities</title><link>https://heroberts.github.io/other/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://heroberts.github.io/other/</guid><description>Workshop organisation Integrating Microdata with Geospatial Approaches, organised together with Marco Helbich and ODISSEI. Reviews I&amp;rsquo;ve reviewed papers for: PLOS ONE; Health and Place, Landscape and Urban Planning, International Journal of Environmental Research and Public Health, Wellbeing, Space and Society, Frontiers in Public Health, Nature Sustainability, Urban Forestry and Urban Greening, Science of the Total Environment, International Journal of Epidemiology, International Journal of Urban Sustainable Development, Sustainability, The Professional Geographer, Population Medicine.</description></item></channel></rss>